Hi, I'm John Dick, president of Realy
Group Real Estate Companies. For 30
years, Realyroup has been meeting the
real estate needs of Indiana. In order
to continue to offer the highest level
of service, I am pleased to announce
that we are now Credential Indiana Realy
Group, an affiliate of the Credential
Real Estate Network. We are honored the
Credential Real Estate Network has
entrusted us with the exclusive right to
use Credential Indiana Realy Group
throughout our state. This is due to our
30 years of top-notch service to our
clients, making buying or selling a home
a pleasurable experience. We are
thrilled the Credential Real Estate
Network offers the best technology,
training, and relocation services, which
Realy Group will use to help you, the
consumer, make the best real estate
decision possible.
We're excited to partner with the
Credential Real Estate Network, a
financially stable, strong company
providing next generation technology and
tools so that we can set a firm
foundation for our future. We are proud
to launch an ambitious growth campaign
that will lead to new jobs for the
people of Indiana in real estate and
related fields. As a bonus, we can now
offer health insurance and other health
rellated benefits along with financial
services to our agents. This is a new
and exciting opportunity for them. Here
are partners from around the state
explaining some of the reasons we have
made this decision.
We have affiliated with Credential Real
Estate and Relocation Services. That
means industry best relocation services
to one real estate brand and one brand
only. Credentials relocation division
provides top-notch relocation services
to Fortune 500 companies across the
globe, including a multitude of
government agencies. And guess what? You
just got a raise. The average sales
price of corporate leads through the
credential relocation services network
is 22% higher than their leading
competition. Also, sending out my
referrals just got easier. We'll be able
to work with some of the most highly
respected mag brokers across the
credential network. And the credential
relocation network doesn't keep half of
your referral fee. Bottom line, better
relocation company, more satisfied
customers, and more money in your
pocket.
We joined uh Credential Real Estate
Network for a number of reasons. Um,
one of the most important reasons is
technology and Credentials technology is
really where we want to be.
They have two programs that we're really
happy with. Uh online sellers advantage
and online buyers advantage. And you're
going to find as an agent there's it's
very simple to use. Uh the simplicity of
it and the effectiveness
your sellers are going to love the fact
that you going to be able to provide
them with everything that's happening in
their neighborhood. What just was
listed, what was expired, a neighbor's
home sold, what did it sell for. This is
the kind of information that they want
and it comes to you as a credential
agent at no cost. It's provided and it's
automatic. All you have to do is set it
up. Really easy. Same type of program
for buyers. They want to know where
things are, how much they cost, what's
changing, and they're going to love
that, too. These things come to us from
Credential as part of the package. No
additional cost. Of course, uh, e-cards,
uh, clients for life type programs, very
easy to set up. You're going to love
those as well. Uh, your back office,
this wasn't in my script, but the back
office, your secretaries and people that
help you every day have one point of
entry. They are going to love that,
which means they're going to be a lot
more friendly to you as well. Uh, we
love the technology. You will, too. The
Credential Real Estate Network is
considered to be a who's who in North
American real estate, featuring many of
our industry's largest, most influential
real estate brokerages.
Credential has the highest average sales
price of all national networks. And as
part of this, we tap into a fertile
referral network which allows us to
learn from and share best practices
with. Some of the very best include
Credential Florida, Credential
California, New Jersey, Credential
Carolas, and many more.
and joining the ranks of the very best I
am certain will be Credential Indiana
Realy Group.
Credential Indiana Realy Group is a
great place to be a realtor and a great
place to work. We have taken an awesome
organization, Realy Group Companies, and
aligned it with 130 years of a solid
foundation credential.
This opportunity will enable all of us
to achieve even higher levels of
excellence and service to our clientele.
In addition to real estate and
relocation services, we have access to
the dream builder program
providing access to insurance and
financial services, a complement of
health care and financial options,
including group health insurance,
individual medical insurance, dental and
vision discount programs, life
insurance,
retirement options, financial planning,
strategies among other resources
assisting our associates to build wealth
and gain security for you and your
family. Thank you.
We want to thank you for listening.
We're pleased and proud of the future
that we have before us. We truly think
we're at the right time at the right
place with the right brand.
[Music]